当我们提到人们对不同波长的光的敏感性时，我们使用a
When we refer to the sensitivity of people to different wavelengths of light we use a
单位称为流明，并定义了流明。
unit called lumens, and lumens are defined.
因此，在555纳米的波长（绿色）下，一瓦特的光会产生一种感觉
So at the wavelength 555 nanometers, which is green, one watt of light creates a sensation
683流明。
of 683 lumens.
在500纳米的波长-蓝色-只有1瓦的光源
At a wavelength of 500 nanometers—which is blue—a one watt light source would only
获得220流明的感觉。
get a sensation of 220 lumens.
所以它是相同数量的电子能量，但如果它集中在那个波长，
So it is the same amount of electronic energy, but if it is concentrated at that wavelength,
如果我们有一瓦特的电子产品，它会给人类观察者带来较小的感觉
it produces a smaller sensation to the human observer and if we had one watt of electronic
在800纳米的能量，它将产生零流明-我们无法看到它，它的结果
energy at 800 nanometers it would produce zero lumens—we can’t see it, it results
根本没有感觉。
in no sensation at all.
所以我们可以看看人类的光度反应，其中有两个：我们的夜晚
So we can look at the human luminosity response and there are two of these: there is our night
时间响应称为暗视响应，白天时间响应称为明视
time response which is called the scotopic response and a day time response, the photopic
响应。
response.
这是我们对特定波长的光的整体感觉，很明显
This is our overall sensation to light at a particular wavelength, and it is clear that
在晚上，我们比较短的波长，比我们更蓝的颜色更敏感
at night we are much more sensitive to shorter wavelengths, the bluer colours, than we are
在白天的时间。
during the day time.
我们之前谈到人类在我们眼睛后面有三种类型的锥形细胞，
We talked before that humans have got three types of cone cells in the backs of our eyes,
短中长波锥。
the short medium and long wavelength cones.
因为我们有三个我们被称为三色，我们有三个意思
Because we have three of them we are referred to as being trichromats, tri meaning we have
我们眼中有三种颜色传感器。
three color sensors in our eyes.
在拥有三种颜色受体的哺乳动物中，人类有些不寻常;大多数哺乳动物
Humans are somewhat unusual amongst mammals in having three color receptors; most mammals
只有两个。
only have two.
并且该图显示了典型哺乳动物的短波长和长波长锥的响应。
And this graph shows the response of the short and long wavelength cones for a typical mammal.
许多鸟类都是四色的;这意味着他们有四种不同类型的锥体细胞
Many birds are tetrachromats; that means that they have four different types of cones cells
这里显示了鸟的锥细胞的反应。
and the response of the bird’s cone cells are shown here.
现在显然，鸟类必须有一些进化优势才能拥有四个锥形细胞。
Now clearly there must be some evolutionary advantage for birds to have four cone cells.
它使他们有更好的辨别色彩的能力。
It gives them a better ability to discriminate colors.
我们可以争辩说，也许对于其他哺乳动物来说，不需要有三个锥形细胞，
We can argue that perhaps for the other mammals there is no need to have three cone cells,
两个就够了。
two is enough.
并非所有人都有完美的三色视觉。
Not all humans have perfect trichromatic vision.
许多人患有色盲，我就是其中之一。
Many humans suffer from color blindness and I am one of those people.
我患有红色，绿色缺陷，这对我来说意味着灵敏度
I suffer from a red, green color deficiency and what that means for me is that the sensitivity
我的中波长锥向右移了一点，所以我的中波长
of my medium wavelength cone is shifted a bit to the right, so my medium wavelength
锥形响应与我的长波长锥响应重叠。
cone response overlaps my long wavelength cone response.
因此，两个锥形响应几乎相等，这使我很难区分
So the two cone responses are almost equal and that makes it very hard for me to distinguish
绿色的红色。
reds from greens.
现在这是一个遗传缺陷，这个特殊的基因位于X染色体的顶端
Now this is a hereditary defect, this particular gene is on the tip of the X chromosome and
通过女性从男性传给男性。
is passed from males to males via females.
色盲在社区中相当普遍，特别是在男性中，
Color blindness is reasonably prevalent in the community, particularly amongst males,
我所拥有的特殊缺陷是人口中6％的人所共有的。
and the particular defect that I have is shared by six per cent of men in the population.
尝试向人们解释色盲是什么感觉是相当困难的。
It is quite difficult to try and explain to people what it is like to be color blind.
这张幻灯片试图向具有正常色觉的人展示世界的外观
This slide is trying to illustrate to somebody with normal color vision how the world looks
有了这些不同类型的颜色缺陷，是否有人缺少他们的L锥，他们的
with these different types of color defects, whether someone is missing their L cone, their
M锥或他们的S锥。
M cone or their S cone.
所以这里我们有光源的光谱，在这种情况下，这是光谱
So here we have the spectrum of the illuminant and in this case this is the spectrum of the
中午的一天太阳在地球表面测量，所以它不是光滑的黑体
noon day sun as measured on the surface of the earth, so it is not the smooth black body
我们之前看过的曲线，由于吸收而产生了肿块和凹凸
curve that we looked at earlier, it has got lumps and bumps in it due to absorption of
大气中分子的光谱部分，这里是亮度
parts of the spectrum by molecules in the atmosphere and here is the luminance of the
从砖块反射的光线。
light that is being reflected from the brick.
而这是从红砖的反射函数乘以得到的
And that is obtained from the reflectance function for the red brick multiplied by the
照度谱。
illuminance spectrum.
因此，来自砖块反射的太阳光具有这种特殊的亮度光谱。
So the light from the sun reflected from the brick has got this particular luminance spectrum.
最后一步是对输入亮度应用许多滤波器或响应函数
The final step is to apply a number of filters or response functions to the incoming luminance
在我们看来，我们应用了三种不同的响应函数。
and in our eye we apply three different response functions.
所以M有三种不同的版本;响应功能。
So there are three different versions of M; the response function.
所以我们首先考虑蓝色响应函数;所以我们采取传入的亮度
So let’s consider firstly the blue response function; so we take the incoming luminance
我们用蓝色锥体的响应过滤它，我们可以在这里看到。
and we filter it with the response of the blue cone and we can see that here.
现在锥体的总响应是亮度乘以的积分
Now the total response of the cone is the integral of the luminance multiplied by the
响应函数，即曲线下方的区域，即此处显示的区域
response function, and that is the area underneath the curve, that is what is shown here as the
坚实的蓝色。
solid mass of blue.
因此，此曲线下面的区域是总能量，它是总响应
So the area underneath this curve is the total amount of energy, it is the total response
对于这种特定的入射亮度，视网膜中的蓝色锥形。
of the blue cone in the retina for this particular incoming luminance.
类似地，对于绿色锥体，我们应用绿锥体响应函数，它自己的版本
Similarly for the green cone, we apply the green cones response function, its own version
兰姆的M然后我们整合曲线下面的区域，那就是
of M of lambda and then we integrate the area underneath the curve, and that is what is
在这里显示为一个坚实的绿色质量，我们对红色锥体做了完全相同的事情。
shown here as a solid mass of green and we do exactly the same thing for the red cone.
我们采用了传入的亮度光谱，对它应用了三个滤波器，集成了
We have taken an incoming luminance spectrum, applied three filters to it, integrated the
这些过滤器的响应和结果是三个数字，红色，绿色的数量
response of those filters and the results are three numbers an amount of red, green
和蓝色。
and blue.
这个过程听起来很复杂，但它做得非常聪明。
This process sounds complicated, but it has done a very clever thing.
如果我们考虑照度的光谱，即光的光谱
If we consider that the spectrum of illuminance, that is, the spectrum of the light that is
从特定物体进入眼睛，它说明了材料特性
entering out eyes from a particular object, it says something about the material properties
那个对象;例如，一个苹果是红色的;植物的叶子是绿色的。
of that object; an apple, for instance, is red; a leaf of a plant is green.
世界上所有这些不同的物体都有不同的光谱。
All of these different objects in the world have got a different spectrum.
但要描述一个频谱，我们需要无数个数字。
But to describe a spectrum we need an infinite number of numbers.
它是波长的连续函数。
It is a continuous function of wavelength.
它是一个无限维信号。
It is an infinite dimensional signal.
但是通过对这个入射光应用三个光谱滤波器并对输出进行积分
But by applying three spectral filters to this incoming light and integrating the output
它传递给每个滤波器之后的信号，我们只剩下了
of the signal after it has passed to each of these filters, we are left simply with
三个数字。
three numbers.
因此，我们将无限维信号简化为三个数或三个
So we have reduced an infinite dimensional signal simply to three numbers or to three
尺寸......进行了大规模的降维。
dimensions … performed a massive dimensionality reduction.
这种降维的结果是模糊的可能性;那是，
A consequence of this dimensionality reduction is the possibility of ambiguity; that is,
有无数个不同的亮度光谱可以准确给出
that there are an infinite number of different luminance spectrum that will give exactly
R，G和B的值相同。
the same values of R, G and B.
我们称这种光谱为metamers;也就是说，不同的光谱可以准确地给你
We refer to such spectra as metamers; that is, different spectra that give you exactly
相同的R，G和B值。
the same R, G and B value.
但显然这不是日常生活中的重大问题;它不是那样的
But clearly this is not a significant problem in everyday life; it is not something that
我们担心或压力，所以我们已经为这个问题找到了一个足够好的解决方案。
we worry or stress about, so we have evolved a good enough solution to the problem.
我们可以通过减少指示它们是什么的信号的维数来识别对象
We can recognise objects by reducing the dimensionality of the signals which indicate what they are
由三个数量组成，三个数字。
made of into just three quantities, three numbers.